What does change look like?
It can be small.
It can be big.
What can we start to imagine
to be a better world?
We’re trying to push forward.
Problem solving is not
like a straight line.
You need to take risks
and think outside the box.
To be able to cope with
the path winding
in a different directions.
To tackle a grand challenge,
you can't just do it by yourself.
The real problems in our world
have not been solved before.
You actually need to come
up with something new.
You need a different skill sets
around you
to help move things forward.
To think differently,
get a different perspective
on what's possible.
It's about reimagining the future,
and the first step is to
not run away from it.
I know that what I'm doing
has a place in the world.
When you're personally invested,
there's a huge sense of purpose.
That takes you a long way.
You need to take that
knowledge into your job,
into community experience,
turning it to a greater purpose.
And we're all here for the same task,
to make a difference in this world.
I want to leave the world
in a better place than I found it.
We have the tools and we have the will.
It just fuels the fire in me.
That drive never goes away.
It's all the reasons
for all the things we've learned,
and all the things we
still need to discover
in our world,
in ourselves
and in each other.
What we need to pass on
is that sense of fearlessness.
Think about things in ways
that they haven't been thought of before.
Because when that light comes on,
that's an amazing moment.